</salt>

School of applied technology



Tomasz Prazniewski

Full-stack developer and a 4th year IT student with a great passion for programming.I am a fast learner and confident working under stress in a high-peaced environment. I am good at paying attention to details and using my analytical skills to solve complex problems, always contributing with my energy and motivation to achieve goals. I am a team player with excellent time management and prioritisation skills.

Have experience with cooperating with industrial automation specialists in Oil and Gas industry. Creating Web Apps, database and OPC servers for their systems.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

General

Java/JavaScript
Ruby/Ruby on Rails

Backend

NodeJS / ExpressJS

REST

GraphQL

MongoDB/PostgreSQL/MySQL/MSSQL/OracleSQL

Prisma ORM

Ruby

Ruby on Rails

Java

Frontend

React, Next.js

Redux

Webpack

HTML Pug

jQuery

CSS/SASS/styled-components

Tools and technologies

Figma

Visual Studio Code

Vmware/ Virtualbox

Mocha/Jest/Cypress

Docker

Git, GitHub

AWS

Cloud Platforms (MongoDB Atlas, ElephantSQL

Netlify, Heroku)

TDD

Agile work methods

Jira/ Confluence

Links

LinkedIn

GitHub

EDUCATION & TRAINING

Full-Stack JavaScript - School of Applied Technology </salt>

May 2022 - Aug 2022

Intensive three month training program for full stack web development with a focus on TDD, mob programming, and applied learning.

Java Basics - SDA bootcamp

Certificated 6months Java bootcamp.

Ruby - CodeAcademy

Certificated online course

Ruby on Rails - CodeAcademy

Certificated online course

RELEVANT WORK EXPERIENCE

IT Specialist - Mercon sp. Z O.O Poland

Nov 2021 - May 2022

- Administrate local network
- Develop Web Applications
- Cooperate with industrial automation specialists

IT Specialist - Aski sp. Z O.O Poland

Jun 2020 - Jun 2021

- Administrate local network
- Administrate Database
- Develop Web Applications
- Meet and negotiate with clients
- Support Team
- Cooperate with industrial automation specialists
- Languages
- English Fluent
- Polish Native